export const Questions = {
    "newQuiz": {
      "_id": "5f7f158d9bdc2d63e81eae99",
      "participants": [
        {
          "_id": "5f7f158d9bdc2d63e81eae98",
          "name": "Robert",
          "score": 0
        }
      ],
      "category": null,
      "timeLimit": 20,
      "questionCount": 20,
      "questions": [
        {
          "choices": [
            "Mouse",
            "Sloth",
            "Frog",
            "Snake"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d5e",
          "question": "Three of these animals hibernate. Which one does not?",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Sloth"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "Fox",
            "Mouse",
            "Opossum",
            "Snail"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d5f",
          "question": "All of these animals are omnivorous except one.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Snail"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "Melursus ursinus",
            "Helarctos malayanus",
            "Ursus minimus",
            "Felis silvestris catus"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d60",
          "question": "Three of these Latin names are names of bears. Which is the odd one?",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Felis silvestris catus"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "Platypus",
            "Dingo",
            "Echidna",
            "Sloth"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d61",
          "question": "These are typical Australian animals except one.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Sloth"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "Lizards",
            "Scorpions",
            "Frogs",
            "Mosquitos"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d62",
          "question": "Representatives of three of these species produce venom of their own. Which is the odd species?",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Mosquitos"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "Penguins",
            "Snakes",
            "Insects",
            "Crustaceans"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d63",
          "question": "Three of these species shed their skin. Which one does not?",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Penguins"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d64",
          "question": "All dogs, cats and birds are colorblind.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "False"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "Polar bears",
            "Foxes",
            "Bats",
            "Elephants"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d65",
          "question": "All of these animals have large ears (relative to their size) except one.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Polar bears"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "10%",
            "20%",
            "15%",
            "25%"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d66",
          "question": "This percentage of all snakes on Earth are lethal to humans.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "15%"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "Herbivorous",
            "Omnivorous",
            "Carnivorous",
            "Vegetarian"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d67",
          "question": "Snakes are this kind of animals.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Carnivorous"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "Breathing",
            "Absorption",
            "Swallowing",
            "Chewing"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d68",
          "question": "Snakes consume their food by means of this process.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Swallowing"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d69",
          "question": "Snakes reproduce only by laying eggs.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "False"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d6a",
          "question": "Snakes are deaf.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "True"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d6b",
          "question": "Snake skin is covered in scales.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "True"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "Invertebrates",
            "Lizards",
            "Reptiles",
            "Mammals"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d6c",
          "question": "Snakes belong to the following category.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Reptiles"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "Pisciculturist",
            "Ornithologist",
            "Ophiologist",
            "Herpetologist"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d6d",
          "question": "A specialist in snakes is called one of these.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Ophiologist"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "Horned adder",
            "Grass snake",
            "Viper",
            "Asp"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d6e",
          "question": "One of the following snakes does not belong to the Viperidae family.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Grass snake"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "True",
            "False"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d6f",
          "question": "Snakes are very likely to attack us, regardless of whether they feel threatened or not.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "False"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "South America and Asia",
            "Asia and Africa",
            "Asia and Australia",
            "South America and Australia"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d70",
          "question": "Cobras are venomous snakes of family Elapidae, that generally inhabit regions of these two continents.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "Asia and Africa"
        },
        {
          "choices": [
            "Balance control",
            "Heat collection from sun rays",
            "Camouflage",
            "More threatening appearance"
          ],
          "_id": "5f7e27359aab364fb4376d71",
          "question": "The cobras most recognizable feature is its hood, a flap of skin and muscle behind the head, believed to serve this purpose.",
          "category": "animals",
          "answer": "More threatening appearance"
        }
      ],
      "__v": 0
    }
  }